Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS.213
Fales Library and Special Collections
Peter Dougherty Collection
1965-2001
1974-1987
Fales Library and Special Collections
MSS.213
12 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
Peter Dougherty is a marketing professional with extensive international experience, including working with MTV from its early days. The Peter Dougherty Collection documents American and British punk rock and hip hop, in addition to Dougherty's work with MTV, and includes audiovisual materials, ephemera, flyers, production manuscripts, and promotional materials.
Arrangement
Paper materials are arranged either chronologically or alphabetically. The collection is arranged into the following five series:
Series I: Sound recordings
Series II: Video recordings
Series III: MTV and Music Business
Subseries A: Branding and Programming
Subseries B: Artist Files
Series IV: Ephemera, Flyers, Programs
Subseries A: Music
Subseries B: Art
Subseries C: Animation and Film
Series V: Personal
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Scope and Content
The Peter Dougherty Collection preserves audio and video recordings documenting British and American punk rock and hip hop. The collection is largely Dougherty's personal music-related collection, from the years before he became a marketing professional. The collection also preserves marketing literature, business manuals, production manuscripts for artists Beastie Boys and Run-D.M.C., in addition to awards programs that document Dougherty's work with MTV Europe. This acquisition also includes Dougherty's personal collection of New York and London art, music, and film events ephemera and promotional materials from the late 1970s through the 1990s.
Biographical Note
Peter Dougherty was born in Queens, NY in 1955, and attended his first rock concert at Shea Stadium during the summer of 1966. After witnessing the madness of The Beatles he then saw Simon and Garfunkel the following summer, and from there, Janis Joplin, The Byrds, Sly and The Family Stone,The Allman Brothers Band, etc. By the mid 1970s, once he was old enough to gain admittance, he starting attending clubs such as Max's Kansas City, CBGB, and Club 82, and began recording these shows.
He later began working with his brother Paul and other friends videotaping bands, and as an assistant in the first 'video lounges' at Peppermint Lounge and Danceteria. In 1982 he started as a production assistant in MTV's creative/promotional department, and remained there until 1990 when he moved to London to become Creative Director of MTV Europe.
Provenance
The collection was acquired by the Fales Library from Peter Dougherty in 2008.
Separated Materials
Printed materials, including zines, have been removed from the collection and will be cataloged as part of the Fales Downtown Book Collection.
Musicians -- 1990-2000; Music |x Competitions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Music |x Societies, etc. |z New York (State) |z New York.; Rap (Music) -- History and criticism.; Punk culture -- New York (State) -- New York; Punk rock music.; Music business |z New York; Music |x Social aspects.; Rock music -- United States -- 1991-2000; Alternative rock music.; Graffiti artists; Graffiti.; Audiocassettes.; Posters.; Postcards.; Scripts (documents); Programs (documents); Art -- Exhibitions.; Beastie Boys; Television (Musical group); Hell, Richard; Smith, Patti; Voidoids (Musical group); Raincoats; Run-D.M.C. (Musical group)
- Series I: Sound recordings, 242013
  - Subseries A: Audio Works, 1976-1985; 197226
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - PA Spot, undated; ID: 213.0001; 197229 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0001, Case 213.0001_pt.1)
      Scope and Content
      Content: Unknown
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Original format: 1/4 in. Audiocassette
      Duration: 90 minutes
      Existence and Location of Copies
      CD access copy available.
      Currently available.
    - 1. Gang War at Fast Lane, Asbury Park NY, September 30 2. J Hanson at Bottomline, September 30, 1978; July 20, 1978; ID: 213.0002; 197230 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0002, Case 213.0002)
      Content: Two sets
      Side A: Ramblin Rose, London Boys, These Boots, Steppin Stone
      Side B: Cant Put Your Arms, Harder, Laughin at [lu], Big Kiss
    - Gang War at MUD, November 27, 1979, ID: 213.0003; 197231 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0003, Case 213.0003_pt.1, Case 213.0003_pt.2)
      Content:
      Ramblin Rose, London, MIA, Endless Party, I'll Go Crazy, Be with the Boys, Harder
      Format: 1/4 in. Audiocassette
      Tape Length: 90 minutes
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please request Part 1 and Part 2.
    - Big Audio Dynamite- Megatop Phoenix, June 14, 1989; ID: 213.0004; 197232 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0004)
      Side A: Start; Rewind; All Mink and No Manners; Union, Jack; Contact; Dragon Town; Baby Don't Apologize; Is Yours Working Yet?; Around the Girl in 80 Ways
      Side B: James Brown; Everybody Needs a Holiday; Mick's a Hippie Burning; House Arrest; The Green Lady; London Bridge; Stalag 123; End
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
    - 1. Big Audio Dynamite live, Paradiso, Amsterdam 2. Alexandria Palace, London, March 23,1990; August 10, 1990; ID: 213.0005; 197233 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0005)
      Side A: Paradiso, Amsterdam 3-23-90 Columbia Records 1991 Demo CD.
      Side B: Alexandra Palace, London 8-10-90 *note: most M. Jones solos edited and remixed by M. Jones & N. Hawkins
      Duration: 60 minutes
    - Big Audio Dynamite - 1. Capital Radio 2. WNEW, December 4, 1985; December 13, 1985; ID: 213.0006; 197234 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0006, Case 213.0006_pt.1, Case 213.0006_pt.2)
      Side A (Dec 4, 1985): unknown
      Side B: Gary Crowley
    - Gang War at Fast Lane, December 2, 1979; ID: 213.0007; 197235 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0007, Case 213.0007_pt.1, Case 213.0007_pt.2)
      Side A: Courageous Cat, Ramblin Rose, London Boys, These Boots, Endless Party, Harder, 10 Commandments, Wayne Still Hates, MIA, Hey Thanks, Pipeline.
      Side B: Just Because, Round & Round, Great Big Kiss, I'll Go Crazy, Can't Put Your Arms, Gypsy, I Can Tell, Courageous Cat
      Currently available. Please request Part 1 and Part 2.
    - Gang War at Heat, December 28, 1979; ID: 213.0008; 197236 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0008, Case 213.0008)
      Content: One Set
      Pipeline, Rambling Rose, London, Endless Party, MIA, Harder They Come, I'll Go Crazy, Rather Be With the Boys, Wayne Still Hates, Little Bit a Whore, Great Big Kiss, Hey Thanx, Can't Put Your Arms, Courageous Cat
    - New York Telephone, undated; ID: 213.0009; 197237 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0009, Case 213.0009)
      Duration: 30 minutes
    - Mick & Co '85, 1985; ID: 213.0010; 197238 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0010, Case 213.0010)
    - Howard Stern, undated; ID: 213.0011; 197239 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0011, Case 213.0011)
      Duration: unknown
    - CaMoy Shalls II, undated; ID: 213.0012; 197240 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0012, Case 213.0012)
    - CaMoy Shalls, undated; ID: 213.0013; 197242 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0013, Case 213.0013_pt.1, Case 213.0013_pt.2)
      [Music], Skin [CreAm], Ad. Bed, Crime Comp., Porcilona, Iron, Bed, Decaf Husband, Without Warning, Rely, Windmill, Drums
    - Hip-Hop (A+B) Rommi Bop!, undated; ID: 213.0014; 197243 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0014, Case 213.0014)
    - "Tastes So Good" File 13, undated; ID: 213.0015; 197244 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0015, Case 213.0015)
      Duration: 10 minutes
    - Gang War - Trude Heller, December 29, ID: 213.0017; 197245 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0017, Case 213.0017)
    - 1. "I Like to Watch" Double D & Steinski 2. Wild Style, undated; ID: 213.0018; 197246 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0018, Case 213.0018)
    - Gang War - Trude Heller's (EMPTY CASE), December 29, 1979; ID: 213.0019; 197247 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0019)
      Contents: One set
      Courageous Cat-cut, Ramblin Rose-cut, Pipeline, Ramblin Rose, London, I'll Go Crazy, Rather Be with the Boys, Endless Party, Harder They Come, Wayne Still Hates, In Every Little Girl, Just Because I'm White
      [EMPTY CASE]
    - 1. MTV Networks 2. Talking Heads, February 11, 1987; 1983; ID: 213.0020; 197248 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0020, Case 213.0020_pt.1, Case 213.0020_pt.2)
      Duration: 120 minutes
    - 1. Bottom Line 2. BAD, undated; ID: 213.0021; 197249 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0021, Case 213.0021)
      Side A: Bottom Line; BAD -US 12" Remix/Bottom Line; BAD -British 12" versions
    - OPAL- "Early Recordings," Serpent Records, 1989; ID: 213.0022; 197250 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0022)
      Side A: Empty Box Blues, She's a Diamond, My Only Friend, Empty Bottles, Grains of Sand, Brigit on Sunday
      Side B: Northern Line, Strange Delight, Fell From the Sun, Harriet Brown, Lulabye, All souls
      Duration: 53 minutes
    - Smokescreens- by J.T.C., Chick Publications, undated; ID: 213.0023; 197251 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0023)
      Content: 1982 By Jack T. Chick
      Duration: 100 minutes
    - untitled, undated; ID: 213.0024; 197252 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0024, Case 213.0024)
    - 1. Double Dee & Steinski "Hip-Hop Mix" 2. "Repo Man" The Ig + opening, January 1985; undated; ID: 213.0025; 197253 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0025, Case 213.0025)
      Side A: "Hip-Hop" Mix Side B: "Repo Man" the Ig and Opening
      Original format: 1/4 in. audiocassette
    - 1. Beastie Boys- Spots 2. Beastie Ads, undated; ID: 213.0026; 197254 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0026, Case 213.0026)
    - VO Disco, August 1981; ID: 213.0027; 197286 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0027, Case 213.0027_pt.1, Case 213.0027_pt.2)
      Side A: with VO and without VO
    - 1. Double D + Steinski "Payoff Mix" 2. Fantasy Three "It's Your Rock", undated; ID: 213.0028; 197584 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0028, Case 213.0028)
      Side A: Payoff Mix
      Side B: It's Your Rock
      Duration: 20 minutes
    - 1. Akabu "Watch Yourself" (inst) 2. Lesson 2 Double Dee + Steinski, undated; ID: 213.0029; 197585 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0029, Case 213.0029)
      Side A: Akabu "Watch Yourself" (instrumental)
      Side B: Lesson 2 Double Dee + Steinski
    - Changin Times Jazz Party '82 Union League Club, New York City, October 7, 1982; ID: 213.0030; 197586 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0030)
      Side A: A Change in the Weather, Ain't Misbehavin', Indiana, Cherry, My Blue Heaven
      Side B: I Got Rhythm, I Want a Little Girl, Sheik of Araby, Take the "A" Train
      Duration: Unknown
    - 1. Alan Squat with stilleto 2. Steading Clubs 7, undated; December 4,1978; ID: 213.0031; 197587 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0031, Case 213.0031_pt.1, Case 213.0031_pt.2)
    - Blue Humans at Max's / Rev, March 19, 1979; ID: 213.0032; 197588 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0032, Case 213.0032)
      Side A: Blue Humans Max's March 19, 1979 / Rev
      Side B: Rev
    - Alan at Max's, July 18, 1980; ID: 213.0033; 197589 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0033, Case 213.0033)
      Content: Two Sets, Unknown
    - 1. Miles Davis at A. Fisher Hall, Live 2. Suicide-MS Lunch at Chase Park, July 5, 1981/October 31, 1981; ID: 213.0034; 197591 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0034, Case 213.0034)
      Side A: Miles Davis July 5, 1981, A. Fisher Hall
      Side B: Suicide/MS Lunch Chase Park October 31, 1981
    - Alan NYE/T.V./Alan/Jan2 Trudie 81 Trudy Hellers New Years Eve, 1980-1981; ID: 213.0035; 197592 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0035, Case 213.0035_pt.1, Case 213.0035_pt.2)
      Side A: Crazy Maniacs, Kung Fu Cowboy, Aint that Nothing
      Side B: Fireball, Kung Fu Cowboy, Jukebox Babe, Heartbeat
    - 1. Suicide at Rock Lounge 2. Danceteria, December 20, 1980/ August 1,1980; ID: 213.0036; 197596 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0036, Case 213.0036_pt.1, Case 213.0036_pt.2)
      Side A: Crazy Maniacs, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Night time, Sweet White Lady, 96 Tears
      Side B: BeBop Kid, Staying Alive, Fast Money Music/Ghost Rider, Sweetheart, Touch Me, Harlem, BeBop Kid, Stayin Alive
    - Alan Max's Doc, May 8, 1981; ID: 213.0037; 197597 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0037, Case 213.0037_pt.1, Case 213.0037_pt.2)
    - Suicide '80 Max's Jan 18 '80, 2 Sets, 1980; ID: 213.0038; 197598 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0038, Case 213.0038_pt.1, Case 213.0038_pt.2)
      Content: Two Sets
      Side A: Harlem, Radiation, Dream Baby Dream, Ghost Rider
      Side B: Dance, 96 Tears, Rocket USA
      Tape Length: 90 mintues
    - [1]-- Suicide Hurrah, December 18, 1979 [2]-- Suicide Heat, February 29, 1980, December 18, 1979, February 29, 1980; ID: 213.0039; 197599 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0039, Case 213.0039_pt.1, Case 213.0039_pt.2)
      Side A: Nightime, Ghost Rider, Dream Baby Dream, Radiation, Harlem, Sweetheart
      Side B: Ghost Rider, Harlem, Sweetheart, Radiation, Rocket U.S.A.
    - [1]-- Suicide Oct 1 '80 Hurrah 1 show [2]-- Suicide Rock Homage 1 show Oct 10 '80, October 1980; ID: 213.0040; 197600 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0040, Case 213.0040_pt.1, Case 213.0040_pt.2)
      Side A: Harlem, Ghost Rider, Cheree, Crazy Maniacs, Radiation, Sweet Little Lady, [RnR]
      Side B: Rocket USA, Crazy Maniacs, Cheree, Harlem, Ghost Rider, RnR is My Life, Sweet White Lady
    - [1]--- Alan Vega Rock City Rock City Dec 26th 1980 [2]--Alan Vega Trude Heller Jan 3 1981, 12/26/80, 1/3/81; ID: 213.0041; 197601 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0041, Case 213.0041)
      Side A: Crazy Maniacs, Kung Fu Cowboy, Love Cry, ByeBye Bayou, Heartbeat, Juke Box Baby, Savage [Mudd] [or]/Niteclub
      Side B. Kung Fu Cowboy, Fireball, Hearbeat, Vietnam Alan, Jukebox Babe
      Access CD available by appointment only.
    - Suicide Max's Dec 28th '78/CBGB June 2 '79 second set, 1978-1979; ID: 213.0042; 197603 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0042, Case 213.0042_pt.1, Case 213.0042_pt.2)
      Side A: Dance. Four Horsemen, Keep Your Dreams, Harlem/Las Vegas, Ray, Sweetheart, (Cont'd), Ghost Rider, Frankie, Johnny
      Side B: Frankie, Dance, Johnny, 96 Tears, Che
    - [1]-- Suicide June May '79 [2]-- CBGB June 2 '79 2nd set/ May '79, 1979; ID: 213.0043; 197604 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0043, Case 213.0043_pt.1, Case 213.0043_pt.2)
      Side A: Frankie, Dance, Johnny, 96 Tears, Che, Las Vegas, Keep your Dreams, Radiation
    - Suicide Hurrah April 11 '80, 1980; ID: 213.0044; 197605 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0044, Case 213.0044)
      Side A: Dance, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Sweetheart, Las Vegas
      Tape Length: 60 minutes
    - [1]-- Suicide Pepermint Lounge Jan 9 '81 [2]-- Ritz with Suicide April 24, 1981; ID: 213.0045; 197606 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0045, Case 213.0045)
      Side A: Rock n' Roll, Crazy Maniacs, Dream Baby Dream, Sweet White Lady, Ghost Rider, Harlem
    - Rev Hurrah 6/11/80, 1980; ID: 213.0046; 197607 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0046, Case 213.0046)
    - [1]-- Suicide May/July 77 CBGB 5/4/77 Max's 7/9/77 2 sets [2]-- Rev Feb. 25 1979 Max's, 1977, 1979; ID: 213.0047; 197608 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0047, Case 213.0047_pt.1, Case 213.0047_pt.2)
      Side A: Ghost Rider, 96 Tears, [Track Unknown], Rocket USA, [Track Unknown], Ghost Rider
      Side B: Fever, Kansas City, [Track Unknown]
    - [1]-- Suicide Mudd Dec 24 '80 [2]-- Suicide Cont'd "80s" Dec 26, '80, 1980; ID: 213.0048; 197609 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0048, Case 213.0048_pt.1, Case 213.0048_pt.2)
      Side A and Side B: Night Time, Ghost Rider, Cheree, Sweet White Lady, Rock n Roll, Night Time, Ave. A, Keep Your Dreams
    - Suicide Thursday (2), Friday (1) CBGB Nov 2 '78, Nov 3 '78, 1978; ID: 213.0049; 197610 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0049, Case 213.0049_pt.1, Case 213.0049_pt.2)
      Side A: Mr. Ray, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Harlem, Night Time, Touch Me- Nice, Las Vegas
      Side B: Four Horsemen, Ghost Rider, [Track Unknown], Ghost Rider, Jesus 4.Four Horsemen, Rocket U.S.A.
    - Suicide '80's Friday the 13th/ June 13 '80 one set, 1980; ID: 213.0050; 197611 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0050, Case 213.0050)
      Side A: Harlem, Ghost Rider, Sweetheart, Rocket U.S.A., Touch Me
    - [1]-- Suicide Mudd 2 Feb 7, 1979 Stealing-Suicide-Van [2]--Alan Annie- Mudd, ID: 213.0051; 197828 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0051, Case 213.0051_pt.1, Case 213.0051_pt.2)
      Side A (Hound Dog): Dance, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Harlem
    - [1]-- Suicide Irving Plaza Jan 24 '81 [2]-- Pepermint Lounge April?, January 24, 1981; ID: 213.0052; 197829 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0052, Case 213.0052)
      Side A: Rock n Roll, Crazy Maniacs, Cheree, Sweet White Lady, Ghost Rider
    - Suicide July 24, 26, 27 '78 Music Machine London, July 24, 26, 27, 1978; ID: 213.0053; 197830 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0053, Case 213.0053)
      Side A and B: Ghost Rider, Rocket USA, Dance, Harlem, Cheree, Ghost Rider, Rocket USA, 96 Tears, Harlem, Ghost Rider, Rocket USA
    - Suicide CBGB June 1 '79, June 1, 1979; ID: 213.0054; 197831 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0054, Case 213.0054_pt.1, Case 213.0054_pt.2)
      Side A: Touch Me, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Las Vegas, Four Horsemen (Radiation)
      Side B: Keep Your Dreams (studio), Rocket U.S.A., Night Time, 96 Tears, Sister Ray, Harlem
    - Suicide July 24, 26, 27 Music Machine, undated; ID: 213.0055; 197832 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0055, Case 213.0055)
      Side A and B: Ghost Rider, Rochet U.S.A., Dance, Harlem, Cheree, Ghost Rider, Rocket U.S.A., 96 Tears, Harlem, Ghost Rider, Rocket U.S.A., Dance, Frankie, Cheree, Sister Ray
    - B-52's/Suicide Nova semiotext(e) 17 Irving Place Friday Dec 1, 1978, December 1, 1978; ID: 213.0056; 197833 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0056, Case 213.0056)
      Side A: Lava, Moon in the Sky, 6060-842, Runnin Around, Rock Lobster, Downtown, 52 Girls, Hero Worship, Devil's in My Car
      Side B: Planet, Harlem, Mama Mama, Sweetheart
    - Waldo Steding 4/79 CBGB April 4, 1979/ 3/81 Ritz March 12, 1981, 1979, 1981; ID: 213.0057; 197834 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0057, Case 213.0057_pt.1, Case 213.0057_pt.2)
      Side A: [Track Unknown], Get Ready, Wake up Mixed Up
    - Jerks/DNA/Dark Day/Blue Humans/Contortions/8 Eyed Spy/Alan+Annie/Rev/Suicide (1977-1979), ID: 213.0058; 197835 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0058, Case 213.0058_pt.1, Case 213.0058_pt.2)
      Side A and B: [1] Jerks w/ James - Max's 8-9-77, DNA 3-11-78 1st perf. [2] Jerks 4-17-79 Maxs, DNA 5-27-79 CBGB, Dark Day 6-13-79 Mud Club [3] Blue Humans 3-19-79 3 trax, Contortions 7-13-78 2 trax, 8 Eyed Spy 12-6-79 2 Trax [4] Alan+Annie 6-13-79 Mud Club, Rev 2-25-79 Maxs, Suicide 2-4-78 CBGB
    - James White & the Contortions, Club 57, Feb 2, 1979, February 2, 1979; ID: 213.0059; 197836 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0059, Case 213.0059)
      Side A: Contort Yourself, Tropical Heatwave, Jaded Side B: Contort Yourself
    - Tom Verlaine, RITZ Oct 8 1981, October 8, 1981; ID: 213.0060; 197837 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0060, Case 213.0060_pt.1, Case 213.0060_pt.2)
      Side A: Kingdom Come, Red Leaves, Souvenir from a Dream
      Side B: Marquee Moon
      Tape Length: Tape Length
    - Television/ John [Cale] New Year's Eve Palladium NYC Dec 31st 1976/ Jan 1st 1977, 1976-1977; ID: 213.0061; 197838 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0061, Case 213.0061_pt.1, Case 213.0061_pt.2)
      Side A: Satisfaction, Fire Engine, Friction, Elevation, Little Johnny Jewel, Adventure, Knockin, Kingdom Come
      Side B: Kingdom Come, Helen of Troy, You Know More Than I Know, Paris 1919, Darling I Need You, Guts, Fear
    - T.V., Max's, Oct 27 '76, sets 1 & 2, First of 2 nites, October 27, 1976; ID: 213.0062; 197839 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0062, Case 213.0062_pt.1, Case 213.0062_pt.2)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Judy, Marquee Moon, Friction, Torn Curtain, Breakin' In my Heart, Hard on Love, Prove it, Venus
      Side B: Venus cont'd, Little Johnny Jewel, Foxhole, Kingdom Come
    - Television, CBGB Dec 7, 1975. 2 sets, copy, December 7, 1975; ID: 213.0063; 197840 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0063, Case 213.0063_pt.1, Case 213.0063_pt.2)
      Tom Verlaine- lead vocals, guitar; Richard Lloyd- guitar, backing vocals; Billy Feeca- drums; Fred Smith- bass, backing vocals
      Side A and B: Fire Engine, Prove It, Oh [Mi] Amore*, Torn Curtain, Let Me Out*, Marquee Moon, See No Evil*, Venus De Milo, Little Johnny Jewel, Friction, Guiding Light*, Kingdom Come *First's/Tape-->Paul"M"/w/Talking Heads
      Format: 1/4 in. audiocassette
    - Television - Mother's, Oct 18th 1975, October 18, 1975; ID: 213.0064; 197841 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0064, Case 213.0064)
      Tom Verlaine- guitar, vocals; Richard Lloyd- guitar; Billy Fecca- drums; Fred Smith-bass
      Side A: Fire Engine, Judy Said, Marquee Moon, Friction, Torn Curtain, Breakin In My Heart.
      Side B: Venus de Milo, Foxhole, Prove It, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel, Hard On Love, Kingdom Come ?
    - Doc Steding '80s Nov 7th 1980, two sets, November 7, 1980; ID: 213.0065; 197842 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0065, Case 213.0065)
      Side A: You Got it, Chase the Dragon, The Joke, (Hound Dog)
    - Paradise Garage: Jerk- Contortions- Hell, Sunday June 18th 1978 -Father's Day, June 18, 1978; ID: 213.0066; 197843 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0066, Case 213.0066_pt.1, Case 213.0066_pt.2)
      Side A: Dish It Out, My Infatuation, Roving Eye, Flip Your Face, Can't Stand Myself, Jaded, Contort Yourself
      Side B: Down at the RnR club, Sports, Kid With the Replaceable Head, Staring in Her Eyes, You've Gotta Lose, Another World, Liars Beware, Blank
    - Contortions July 13 CBGB/ July 14 Millenium - 1978, ID: 213.0067; 197844 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0067, Case 213.0067_pt.1, Case 213.0067_pt.2)
      George- bass, Jody- guitar, Patti- slide guitar
      Side A and B: Roving Eye, My Infatuation, Contort Yourself, Throw Me Away, Jaded But So in Love, Contort Yourself
    - Glen's Desperation Benefit, Mudd, Nov 20 1980, November 20, 1980; ID: 213.0068; 197845 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0068, Case 213.0068_pt.1, Case 213.0068_pt.2)
    - Teenage Jesus and the Jerks w/ J. Sigfried: Nov 15 1977- Max's only set, Jan 13 1978- CBGB two sets., 1977, 1978; ID: 213.0069; 197846 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0069, Case 213.0069_pt.1, Case 213.0069_pt.2)
      Side A: Three Jerks Sets
      Side B: Jerks with James
    - Doc & The Boys, Heat, March 14 '80, March 14, 1980; ID: 213.0070; 197847 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0070, Case 213.0070_pt.1, Case 213.0070_pt.2)
      Content: TV Party - Doc & The Boys
    - Steding, Hurrah - Sept [24] 1979; 8 Eyed Spy - Max's Dec 6 1979 (one set only), ID: 213.0071; 197848 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0071, Case 213.0071)
      Side A: Steding Hurrah Sep 24, '79; Suicide Midnight Special
      Side B: 8-eyed Spy Max's Dec 6, '79, one set only
    - Tirez Tirez Live (Inroads) June 12 '81/ Savage T.V. Party, Easter '81 [Pep Lounge?], 1981; ID: 213.0072; 197849 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0072, Case 213.0072_pt.1, Case 213.0072_pt.2)
    - Doc Trax Dec 3 '80 plus Suicide 80s excerpts & 2 sets slides show soundtrack, 1980; ID: 213.0073; 197850 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0073, Case 213.0073_pt.1, Case 213.0073_pt.2)
    - Contortions- CBGB 1st set 2/4/78. Blessed- Maxs March 5th 1978 1st set. Fleshtones- CBGB 2/4/78, ID: 213.0074; 197851 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0074, Case 213.0074_pt.1, Case 213.0074_pt.2)
      Side A: I Don't Wanna Be Happy, My infatuation
    - X Magazine Benefit, Millenium E. 4th st * Erasers w/Quinne - Screamers, CBGB Nove 17th '78, November 17, 1978; ID: 213.0075; 197852 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0075, Case 213.0075_pt.1, Case 213.0075_pt.2)
      Side A: Funtime*, DNA, Roving Eye, Love Twice Removed
      Side B: (Contortions Cont'd); Throw Me Away, Jaded But So in Love, Content Yourself, SCREAMERS
    - Contortions 2/78 April 24, 1978 Max's/ New Aug 22 '79 Max's, Apr 24, 1979, Aug 22, 1979; ID: 213.0076; 197853 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0076, Case 213.0076_pt.1, Case 213.0076_pt.2)
      Side A: Dish It Out, My Infatuation, I Don't Wanna Be Happy
      Side B: Good Times